<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on SuperTsumu</title>
    <link>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on SuperTsumu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:45:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CloudC2</title>
      <link>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/cloudc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:45:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/cloudc2/</guid>
      <description>Home
How to make a command-and-control (C2) server on the cloud A command-and-control server (C2) is a server where hackers control their victim’s compromised computers via bind/reverse shells. They can come in the form of a simple netcat instance or fully developed frameworks that feature exploitation scripts such as Meterpreter and PowerSploit.
In this article, I will be demonstrating how I hosted my C2 server on the cloud and its capabilities using the Linode cloud hosting service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obfuscation with Villain</title>
      <link>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/villain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:45:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/villain/</guid>
      <description>Home
Windows Defender Bypass with Villain and Obfuscation (14/12/2022) Windows Defender is a signature based antimalware system. This means that it checks programs against a library of previously identified malware to locate malicious software. Because of this, attackers can find ways to bypass Windows Defender by either creating new payloads or encoding/obfuscating existing payloads beyond recognition. Villain Click here to watch it in action Note: I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you&amp;rsquo;re going to try this out, please turn off Windows Defender&amp;rsquo;s automatic sample submission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>revducky</title>
      <link>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/revducky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:45:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/revducky/</guid>
      <description>Home
I made a rubber ducky reverse shell for &lt;$10 (Win-10) USB Rubber Ducky by Hak5 The Hak5 USB Rubber Ducky is a small microcontroller that acts as a keyboard and automatically enters pre-programmed keystrokes. The original Rubber Ducky by Hak5 will cost you 60$. I will be making one for under 10$ with an Arduino pro micro and writing a script to start and conceal a Windows 10 reverse shell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2 Tunneling</title>
      <link>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/tunnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://supertsumu.github.io/projects/tunnel/</guid>
      <description>Home
[OPSEC] Tunneling C2 traffic </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
